https://www.sherry-lehmann.com/privacy_policy

Menu
Toggle Nav
WINESMost PopularBordeauxBurgundyChampagneAmericanItalianSpainBordeauxBurgundyChampagneAmericanItalianSpainBy TypeRedWhiteRoséRedWhiteRoséBy CountryFranceUSAItalySpainMoreFranceUSAItalySpainMoreBy VarietalPinot NoirBordeaux RedChardonnaySparklingCabernet SauvignonBlendMorePinot NoirBordeaux RedChardonnaySparklingCabernet SauvignonBlendMoreBy PriceLess Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More than $120Less Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More than $120Most PopularBordeauxBurgundyChampagneAmericanItalianSpainBordeauxBurgundyChampagneAmericanItalianSpainBy TypeRedWhiteRoséRedWhiteRoséBy CountryFranceUSAItalySpainMoreFranceUSAItalySpainMoreBy VarietalPinot NoirBordeaux RedChardonnaySparklingCabernet SauvignonBlendMorePinot NoirBordeaux RedChardonnaySparklingCabernet SauvignonBlendMoreBy PriceLess Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More than $120Less Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More than $120CHAMPAGNEMost PopularChampagneRose ChampagneGrower ChampagneBig BottlesSparklingProseccoChampagneRose ChampagneGrower ChampagneBig BottlesSparklingProseccoBy CountryFranceUSAItalySpainMoreFranceUSAItalySpainMoreBy ProducerDom PerignonPiper HeidsieckTaittingerMoet & ChandonScharffenbergerZardettoMoreDom PerignonPiper HeidsieckTaittingerMoet & ChandonScharffenbergerZardettoMoreBy PriceLess Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More Than $120Less Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More Than $120Most PopularChampagneRose ChampagneGrower ChampagneBig BottlesSparklingProseccoChampagneRose ChampagneGrower ChampagneBig BottlesSparklingProseccoBy CountryFranceUSAItalySpainMoreFranceUSAItalySpainMoreBy ProducerDom PerignonPiper HeidsieckTaittingerMoet & ChandonScharffenbergerZardettoMoreDom PerignonPiper HeidsieckTaittingerMoet & ChandonScharffenbergerZardettoMoreBy PriceLess Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More Than $120Less Than $30$30 - $60$60 - $90$90 - $120More Than $120SAMPLERSSPIRITSBy TypeSingle MaltVodkaGinTequilaBourbonBlended ScotchMoreSingle MaltVodkaGinTequilaBourbonBlended ScotchMoreBy CountryUnited KingdomUSAItalyFranceMoreUnited KingdomUSAItalyFranceMoreBy ProducerJohnnie WalkerHennessyThe MacallanGlenmorangieCasa DragonesPatronMoreJohnnie WalkerHennessyThe MacallanGlenmorangieCasa DragonesPatronMoreBy TypeSingle MaltVodkaGinTequilaBourbonBlended ScotchMoreSingle MaltVodkaGinTequilaBourbonBlended ScotchMoreBy CountryUnited KingdomUSAItalyFranceMoreUnited KingdomUSAItalyFranceMoreBy ProducerJohnnie WalkerHennessyThe MacallanGlenmorangieCasa DragonesPatronMoreJohnnie WalkerHennessyThe MacallanGlenmorangieCasa DragonesPatronMoreBIG BOTTLESEVENTSGIFTSGift ShopSherry-Lehmann Gift CardAccessoriesGlasswareCorkscrewsBooksBasket & ContainersYetiOther AccessoriesGlasswareCorkscrewsBooksBasket & ContainersYetiOther AccessoriesGift ShopSherry-Lehmann Gift CardAccessoriesGlasswareCorkscrewsBooksBasket & ContainersYetiOther AccessoriesGlasswareCorkscrewsBooksBasket & ContainersYetiOther Accessories
Search
Search
Search
SEARCH
Cart
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Sherry-Lehmann respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our website. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide Sherry-Lehmann will be known only to two parties: you and Sherry-Lehmann. The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. Personal information includes your name, street and email addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here.
This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
Traffic Data
Each time a visitor comes to the Sherry-Lehmann.com website, our server—like most on the Web—collects some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from aol.com or earthlink.net, etc.), and browser and platform type (e.g., an Internet Explorer browser on a Windows XP computer).
We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows about visitors and visits into group data).
Use of Cookies
Sherry-Lehmann.com assigns “cookies” to your web browser. Cookies are small text files that allow a website to remember who a visitor is and therefore not require them to type in personal information over and over again.
Announcements
After signing up to receive a Sherry-Lehmann announcement by email, users will start receiving these announcements on a regular basis. We collect subscribers' email addresses in order to distribute those announcements. Users can choose to unsubscribe from Sherry-Lehmann announcements at any time by following the “Unsubscribe” instructions found in each email.
Other Disclosure of Personal Information
Sherry-Lehmann will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent, except as described in this Privacy Policy, or as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority.
Email
If you would like to unsubscribe from Sherry-Lehmann email announcements, click the "Unsubscribe" link at the top of any of our emails.Or send an email to
newsletter@sherry-lehmann.com
with GOODBYE in the Subject line.
© Sherry-Lehmann Wine & Spirits. All rights reserved.
(212) 838-7500
505 Park Avenue, New York, NY 10022
Never8 eCommerce & eBusiness
